Guide to the Time Inc. Corporate Editorial Records 1944-2003 (bulk 1959-1994) MS 3009-RG 6
New-York Historical Society
- Series VI.B. Special Assistant to the Editor-in-Chief Marshall Loeb Files, 1981-1986; 2 Linear feet in 2 record cartons
  - National Magazine Awards: 1986, 1985-1986 (Offsite-box 3714, Folder 27)
  - National Portrait Gallery, 1985 (Offsite-box 3714, Folder 28)
  - Patterson, Martha Priddy, 1985 (Offsite-box 3714, Folder 29)
  - People Magazine Book, 1985 (Offsite-box 3714, Folder 30)
  - People: Performance Review Manual, 1984 (Offsite-box 3714, Folder 31)
  - People: Spanish People, 1984-1985 (Offsite-box 3714, Folder 32)
  - People: Spinoff, 1986 (Offsite-box 3714, Folder 33)
  - People: Television Proposal, 1985 (Offsite-box 3714, Folder 34)
  - Prendergast, Curt, 1984-1985 (Offsite-box 3714, Folder 35)
  - Prendergast, Curt: Contract [RESTRICTED], 1980-1984 (Offsite-box R17)
  - Personnel, circa 1985 (Offsite-box 3714, Folder 36)
  - Robertson, Wyndham, 1985-1986 (Offsite-box 3714, Folder 37)
  - Selling Areas-Marketing Inc. (SAMI), 1985 (Offsite-box 3714, Folder 38)
  - Smithsonian's Hollywood Exhibit, 1985 (Offsite-box 3714, Folder 39)
  - Southern Living Creative Ideas, 1985-1986 (Offsite-box 3714, Folder 40)
  - Studies: Consumer Trends, circa 1984 (Offsite-box 3714, Folder 41)
  - Studies: Corporate Identity Study, 1984 (Offsite-box 3715, Folder 1)
  - Studies: Magazine Group: Strategic Planning: Industry Map, 1984 (Offsite-box 3715, Folder 2)
  - Summer Internship Program, 1984-1985 (Offsite-box 3715, Folder 3)
  - Takeover Conference, 1984-1986 (Offsite-box 3715, Folder 4-5)
  - Time Education Television Program, 1985 (Offsite-box 3715, Folder 6)
  - Third Man Duties, circa 1985 (Offsite-box 3715, Folder 7)
  - Unlisted Market Service Corp.: Business and Financial Plan, 1985? (Offsite-box 3715, Folder 8)
  - United Press International (UPI)/Time Contract, 1984-1986 (Offsite-box 3715, Folder 9)
  - United Press International (UPI)/Time Contract [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R17)
  - Urban Foundation (South Africa), 1985 (Offsite-box 3715, Folder 10)
  - Value Line, 1985 (Offsite-box 3715, Folder 11)
  - Videocassettes, 1986 (Offsite-box 3715, Folder 12-13)
    Videocassettes includes the "Business Case on Viability of Videobooks" and a transcript of the Time-Life Books "Video Directions" conference.
  - Video, 1981-1985 (Offsite-box 3715, Folder 14)
  - Wilson, Donald (Consultant): General, 1981-1982 (Offsite-box 3715, Folder 15-17)
  - Wilson, Donald (Consultant): Transcript of Presentation to Magazine Group, 1981 (Offsite-box 3715, Folder 18-19)
  - Winners International, 1986 (Offsite-box 3715, Folder 20)
  - Winston, Susan, 1985 (Offsite-box 3715, Folder 21)
  - Writer Apprentice Program, 1984-1985 (Offsite-box 3715, Folder 22)